All right, let's play one more time, okay?
好, 好, 再玩一次, 好嗎？
And remember, if I win, you do not move to Paris.
如果我贏了你就不能去巴黎
Okay. I can't believe I'm risking this again, but you're on.
好吧, 我就再冒一次險
All right, Joe, you remember the rules. Heads, I win. Tails, you lose.
別忘了規則, 喬伊, 正面是我贏, 反面是你輸
Just flip.
快點扔吧
-Tails! -Damn it!
-啊, 是反面  -該死的！
So we thought we'd throw you a little going-away party around 7.
嘿, 我們為你準備了一個送行會, 7點鐘開始
Oh, that sounds good.
哦, 聽起來不錯嘛
Hey, Rach, you're leaving tomorrow. Shouldn't you be packing?
嘿, 瑞秋, 你明天就要走了, 現在還不開始收拾？
-It's all done. -Oh, yeah, right.
-已經收拾好了  -哈, 是嘛？
And after I took a shower this morning, I just threw my towel on the floor.
今天早上我沖澡的時候, 我把毛巾扔在地上了...
-Oh, God, it hurts to even joke about it. -I know.
-哦, 天哪, 就算是開玩笑我都心疼  -我知道
Honey, seriously, I did it all. The luggage that I'm taking is in the bedroom.
莫妮卡, 我是說真的 我全都收拾好了  要帶的行李都在臥室裡
This is Emma's Paris stuff. These are the boxes that I'm having shipped..
這些是艾瑪要在巴黎用的東西 這些箱子都是要托運的
and that's the sandwich I made for the plane.
那個是我打算飛機上吃的三明治
Which could've used a little more mustard.
不過應該多加些芥末
-Okay, so you've done some good work. -Yeah.
-看起來你幹得還不賴  -是啊
What about your carryons?
你的手提行李呢？
Oh, well, everything that I need is in here..
哦, 需要的東西全都在這個包裡
and my travel documents are on the counter..
而旅行要用到的文件和材料都在檯子上
organized in the order that I will be needing them.
我已經把它們按照使用順序排好了
Oh, my God. I have nothing left to teach you.
哦, 天啊, 我好像沒什麼要提醒你的了
-Where's your passport? -It should be next to my plane ticket.
-你的護照呢？ -應該跟我的機票在一塊
-Well, it's not. -What? Well, maybe I put it in here?
-嗯...沒有啊? -沒有嗎？也許我放在這裡了？
Oh, it's not in there!
噢, 沒有, 不在這兒...哦， 不會吧
Oh, no, I must have packed it in one of these boxes!
我肯定是把它封在這些箱子裡了...
-Here, let me help you. -Shoot.
-我來幫你  -倒霉...
I can't believe I did this.
真不敢相信...我怎麼會放在這兒的...
At what point did it stop being funny that I took her passport?
玩笑是不是開過頭了...
The One With Rachel's Going Away Party
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Oh, wow, can you believe you're only three weeks away?
天哪, 只剩三個禮拜了, 真是讓人難以相信啊
I know.
是啊
-You don't mind me touching your belly? -I don't mind you touching my belly..
-你不介意我摸你的肚子吧？ -我不介意你摸我的肚子
but your hand's kind of blocking the part where the baby's gonna come out.
但是你的手現在好像 已經摸到孩子出生的地方了
-Hey! -Hey.
-嘿  -嗨
Hi, Erica. Welcome back to town. Wow, look how big you've gotten.
嘿, 艾瑞卡, 歡迎回來  哦, 你都已經變得這麼豐滿了！
That's because I'm pregnant.
這是因為我懷孕了！
-Right. No, I understand. -Oh, okay.
-哦, 對, 沒錯, 我知道  -哦, 哈
I'm just always afraid that people think I'm just fat with big breasts.
我就是怕別人以為我本來就是個胸大的胖妞
No, no, I knew.
哦, 不, 不, 我不會的
-Okay, well, stop staring at them. -She brought them up.
-嘿, 別死盯著人家（的胸）啊 -是她先提起這事兒來的
I didn't realize you were coming back so soon.
你怎麼這麼快就回來了？
In a couple weeks I won't be able to travel.
再過兩個星期我就不能旅行了
And I wanted her to get to know the doctors and get settled into the hotel.
我想讓她先見見醫生, 然後在酒店安頓下來
-Why isn't she staying with you guys? -Because we're moving in a couple days.
-酒店？為什麼不讓她和你們一起住？ -不行啊, 因為我們馬上就要搬了
Plus, hotels are fun! My room has this little fridge full of free snacks.
啊, 酒店裡很好玩兒啊 我的房間裡有一個小冰櫃 裡面塞滿了零食, 都是免費的
Erica, those things aren't free.
艾瑞卡, 那些零食可不是免費的
They have one of the highest markups of any consumer product..
實際上, 酒店裡的食品是最貴...
Ross, she's giving us her baby. She can eat you if she wants.
羅斯, 她正準備給我們生個孩子  就算她把你吃了都無所謂
I'll be right back.
我馬上就回來
Oh, man, I can't believe you guys are leaving this place.
哎, 真不敢相信你們就要離開這兒了
I know. I know.
是啊...
You know, you could take it if you want. The lease is still in Nana's name.
如果你想要這間公寓的話, 你可以住進來 連名字都不用改（公寓是以莫妮卡祖母的姓蓋勒登記的）
No, no. This will always be your place. It would be too sad.
哦, 不, 不 這裡永遠是屬於你們的  住在這兒太傷感了
Plus, how much a month does it cost to feed Joey?
而且... 每個月喬伊會吃掉多少錢？
Yeah, it takes two incomes.
兩個人掙的都不夠
Is Chandler here? We talked about catching a movie.
嘿, 錢德在麼？ 我們約好了要去看電影的
Oh, no, he doesn't have time for that.
他可沒那個閒工夫
You can go help him and Joey pack up the guest room.
如果你有空 你可以去客房幫他和喬伊一起收拾東西
Packing. Sexy cheerleader comedy.
恩...是收拾東西呢？ 還是去看電影裡性感的女啦啦隊員呢？
Helpful brother. Creepy loner at teen movie.
恩...是一個好哥哥呢？ 還是一個去看青春片的老衰人？
"Creepy.."
（×＃※￥◎（×￥....
-What are you guys doing? -Try it. I can't feel a thing.
-你們倆幹嗎呢？ -快來試試！我一點兒都不疼！！
Are you kidding?
你們開什麼玩笑！
-This is packing? -We're taking a break.
-這叫收拾東西麼？！ -我們累了, 正在休息呢
From?
怎麼會累著的？
Jumping on the bed.
...剛才在床上蹦來著...
All right, Rachel's party is in a couple of hours, and there's a lot to do.
好了, 瑞秋的送行會就快開始了 我們有一堆兒事情要做呢！
Ross, you've got Geller blood. You're in charge of these yahoos.
羅斯, 別忘了你身上留著蓋勒家的血  你負責看著這兩個傢伙！
-You got it. -All right.
-知道了  -好吧
All right, she's right. We gotta get serious.
她說的對, 我們得認真一點兒
Let's put Styrofoam peanuts down his pants and kick him!
讓我們把這個塞到他的褲襠裡, 然後踢他！
No, guys, she's right. We should get to work. I'll take stuff out of the closet.
不, 不, 不 她說的對 我們得開始工作了 我來把櫃子裡的東西搬出來
Joey, you pack them, and Ross, you repack whatever Joey packs.
喬伊你負責打包, 羅斯你負責把所有喬伊打過的包重打一遍
You guys hear a ringing?
你們聽到有什麼東西嗡嗡叫麼？
-What the hell is this? -Hey, handcuffs. And fur-lined. Nice.
-這是什麼鬼玩意兒？ -嘿, 手銬, 還裹著皮毛！ 真有你們的！
I didn't know you guys had it in you.
不知道你們還來這一手兒...
Chandler, you don't have a sister, so you can't understand..
錢德, 你沒有妹妹 所以你大概不能體會我現在的心情...
how much this bums me out.
不能體會我現在多鬧心
I didn't know Monica had these.
我不知道莫妮卡什麼時候開始有這玩意兒的
Maybe she used them with another boyfriend. Maybe Richard.
嗯, 也許這是她用在別的男人身上的  也許是Richard呢...
Why would she use them with Richard and not me? I can be kinky.
為什麼她和理查德玩兒這個, 卻不跟我玩兒？
I once did a naked dance for her with scarves.
有一次我還光著身子給她跳舞來著 當時我用的是領帶
Bumming hard, guys. Bumming hard.
越來越過分了...
-Hey. -Hey. Where's Mike?
-嘿  -嗨 麥克呢？
Oh, he has a gig.
他有一場演出...
It's kind of like being married to a rock star, you know?
我越來越覺得自己像是個搖滾歌星的老婆了...
My husband has a gig.
我老公有場演出!
Yeah? Where is it?
在哪兒演出啊？
Oh, he's playing organ for a children's roller-skating party.
哦, 是一個少兒滾軸溜冰的聚會  他去那兒彈琴
Rock on!
還真夠勁兒啊!
Wow, this is quite a spread. What is all this stuff?
哦, 擺了這麼大一桌子 這些都是什麼啊？
I thought this would be a great opportunity to use up all the food..
嗯, 我覺得今天的晚會是一個好機會
that I don't want to move to the new house with me.
我可以把所有不想帶走的食物全都用了...
So enjoy. Smoked oyster casserole with a breakfast-cereal crust.
那麼...盡情享受吧  熏牡蠣卷拌早餐麥片
Kidney beans in their own juices, and for dessert, a questionable orange.
四季豆加豆汁兒 然後甜點是...一個過期的橙子
Well, I think I speak for everyone when I say:
那麼, 我應該替大伙說話了
-Hey. -Hey.
-嘿 -嘿
-Where's Rach? -She's putting Emma down.
-嘿, 瑞秋呢？ -她在哄艾瑪睡覺呢
She'll be over in a second. It just hit her that she's leaving.
馬上就過來  可能是因為要走了, 她現在情緒有點激動
She's kind of emotional, so no one say anything to set her off, okay?
所以別刺激她, 記住了麼？
-Hey, Rach. -Hey.
-嘿, 瑞秋 -嗨
There she is.
在這呢
Hi, you guys.
嗨, 大家好
What did I just say?
我剛才怎麼交待你們的！！！
Oh, no, no, no, it's okay. It's okay. I'm gonna be fine.
不, 不, 我沒事
-Come here, I'll make you a drink. -Okay.
-過來, 我給你弄點喝的  -好的
Oh, man, I can't believe she's actually leaving.
哦, 天哪, 我真不敢相信, 她真的要走了
How am I gonna say goodbye to Rachel?
讓我怎麼開得了口說再見啊
I know, she's been such a big part of my life.
她對我來說這麼重要...
It feels like when Melrose Place got cancelled.
就好像梅爾羅斯(美國馬薩諸塞州東部一城市) 要被剔除了
I mean..
我是說..
Forget it, I miss Melrose Place.
忘了吧, 我想念梅爾羅斯
-I had a chance to stop her too. -Yeah?
-我本來有機會阻止她的, -是嗎？
Who loses 57 coin tosses in a row? You know?
沒想到猜鋼崩兒我會連輸47次
Heads, she wins. Tails, I lose.
正面她贏, 反面我輸嘛...
Wait a minute.
等等...
-Yes, Joe? -I forgot to pick up my dry cleaning.
-怎麼了, 喬伊? -我忘了把衣服從乾洗店拿回來了...
So you doing okay?
你還好吧？
Well, I've been better. You guys are gonna come visit, right?
嗯, 我好多了 你們都會來看我的, 對不對?
Yes! You know, in six months, the statute of limitations runs out..
當然了！再過6個月我的禁令就過期了
and I can travel internationally again.
到時候我又可以作國際旅行了
-I'm gonna miss you so much. -I know.
-我一定會很想你的！ -我也是
You know what? I have some goodbye stuff that I wanted to say..
你知道麼, 我對你們每個人都有些告別的話要說
to each of you. I was gonna save it till the end of the night, but come here.
我本來打算在結束的時候說的, 但是...跟我來
Hey, what do you think they're doing in there?
嘿, 你們說她們到屋裡去幹嗎？
If I had to guess, I'd say..
嗯, 照我看來
Rachel's putting on the bubble wrap, and Phoebe's doing the punching.
肯定是瑞秋戴上塑料泡沫, 然後菲比來動手打
Phoebe, I don't even know where to start.
哦, 菲比, 我真不知道應該怎麼開口
Okay, well, before you do, I know we weren't supposed to get you presents..
嗯, 這樣吧 我知道今天本來不需要給你準備禮物的
but I do have something for you.
但我還是準備了一個
-What is it? -Well, it's a cotton swab..
-哦, 哦, 這是什麼？ -是一個棉花棒
with a bit of my saliva on it..
上面沾了些我的口水
so that if they perfect the cloning process while you're over there..
這樣一來 如果你在巴黎的時候發現那邊的克隆技術成熟了
you can use the DNA to create your own Phoebe.
你就可以用這上面的DNA來另外做一個菲比
I'm gonna throw this away..
啊...我可能會把這個扔掉...
but thank you so much for the gesture.
但是我很感謝你這份心意...
Chandler?
錢德？
I was just in our bedroom, and I found these on my pillow.
我剛才在臥室的枕頭上發現了這個？
Oh, yes, I decided to leave those out for you in case Richard stops by..
哦, 我決定把這個先給你留著  萬一哪天Richard過來
and you want to engage in a little light bondage and mustache play.
你可以跟他的鬍子一起玩
What? These aren't mine.
你說什麼呢？這不是我的！
Oh, yeah, right!
啊？是嗎？
Good luck getting another scarf dance from me.
以後休想再讓我給你跳領帶舞了！
That would be a terrible punishment.
這種「懲罰」太可怕了...
But I'm serious, I've never seen these before.
我是說真的 我以前從來沒見過這東西
Really? Then what are they doing in our guest room?
真的嗎？那它怎麼會出現在我們的客房裡的？
Rachel used to live in that room.
瑞秋曾經在那裡住過
Rachel. With handcuffs.
瑞秋...戴著手銬...
Interesting.
真不錯...
Joey's bare ass.
光著屁股的喬伊!!!
Well played.
真有你的
-I love you, Phoebe. -I love you too.
-我愛你, 菲比! -我也愛你!
Please..
你..
Please don't..
你可千萬...千萬...
Don't turn into, you know, a French bitch.
別...別變成一個...法國婊子...
I won't.
好的
All right. Well, if I'm gonna do this, I better keep going.
我得繼續找其他人了
-Okay. -Okay.
-好的 -好的
-Monica? -Yeah?
-莫妮卡 -哦！
-Will you come with me for a minute? -Sure.
-跟我進來一下好嗎？ -當然
-Are you wearing waterproof mascara? -No.
-你的面霜是防水的麼？ -不是啊
Oh, you're so screwed.
哦, 你完蛋了
Hey.
嘿
What was that all about?
這是怎麼回事？
She's gonna say goodbye to each of us individually.
她打算跟我們每個人單獨告別
Are you kidding? Oh, my God.
哦, 開什麼玩笑, 天哪！
Yeah, I know. It's gonna be even worse for you. God.
是啊, 我知道, 輪到你的時候可能會更糟
Well, just get ready to do some serious crying.
天哪, 準備好好大哭一場吧
Man, I'm not gonna be able to handle this.
天哪, 我怕我會撐不過去...
Now I know how my students feel at the end of each year.
我現在終於知道每個學期末我的學生們的感受了
And why they act out by giving me such bad evaluations.
我猜他們是因為太捨不得我了 所以才會（在教師評定中）給我打那麼低的分數
Mon. Okay.
莫妮卡, 好吧
I better just say what it is I'm gonna say.
我就直說了 我想說的是...
None of the amazing things that have happened to me in the last 10 years..
如果沒有你, 我在過去十年裡
would have happened if it wasn't for you.
我不可能會這麼幸福
No one has been more like a sister to me.
一直以來, 你對我來說就像是姐姐一樣
I know what you mean.
我知道
You're like a sister to me too.
我也一直把你當作妹妹
I don't know what I'm going to do without you.
我不知道沒有你我會怎麼辦！
You're the greatest friend I ever had.
你是我最好的朋友
seeing you every day.
每天見到的
What?
你說什麼？
I.. I.. I..
我, 我…
see you every day!
每天都看見你
That is so sweet!
太讓我感動了！！！
Oh, no, she took down Monica.
哦, 她連莫妮卡都搞定了
And I'm the crier in the family.
要知道 在蓋勒家我是最愛哭的
Oh, God, I could be next.
哦, 天哪, 可能該輪到我了
Maybe she won't talk to me if it looks like we're deep in conversation.
如果我跟你說話, 她可能就不選我了
Oh, so that thing you said about the thing..
哦, 那麼說你之前說的那個什麼
it really made me think about that other thing.
讓我想起了那個什麼
-Rach? -Oh, it's okay, Chandler's talking to her.
-瑞秋？ -好了, 看起來錢德找上她了
I really made you think about that thing, huh?
你想起了哪個什麼啊？
Rach, I think I have something that belongs to you.
瑞秋, 我想這個應該是你的吧？
I'm sure gonna miss pretending to laugh at your weird jokes that I don't get.
哈, 你的笑話又來了 每次我都得逼著自己樂  我將來一定會懷念這種感覺
No, no, they're really yours. We found them in your old room.
不, 不, 這真的是你的  我們是在你住過的房間裡找到的
These aren't mine. Maybe Monica used to use them with..
但這不是我的啊 也許這是莫妮卡以前和...
Don't say Richard.
別提Richard!
Well, if they're not Monica's and they're not yours, then whose are they?
如果這不是莫妮卡的, 也不是你的, 那是誰的呢？
I think you're forgetting the kinkiest former resident of that room.
我想你大概忘了 在客房裡住過的所有人裡面, 誰是最變態的？
-Phoebe! -Yeah!
-菲比 -哦 !
I think these are yours.
我想這個是你的吧？
These are not mine. Look how flimsy they are. Come on.
這不是我的! 這麼鬆鬆垮垮的
My God, you try to hang a guy from a water pipe with these..
如果你用這個把人栓在水管上面
they'll snap like a piece of licorice.
他輕而易舉就跑掉了
-Can I talk to you alone for a minute? -Sure.
-我能單獨跟你談談麼？ -當然
You don't really handcuff guys to water pipes do you?
你不會真的把人拷在水管上吧？
Where do you think Mike really is?
你以為麥克現在在哪兒？
Oh, honey..
哦, 親愛的
Let me just saying something because once we get into this..
讓我先說兩句吧  要不然待會兒...
I'm gonna get all uncomfortable and probably make some stupid joke.
一旦我覺得不自然 可能又該開始開無聊的玩笑了
I just want to say that I.. I love you.
我就是想說, 我...我愛你
And I'm gonna miss you.
還有就是, 我會想你的
And I'm so sad that you're leaving.
你就這麼走了, 我真的很難過
Oh, you know what?
哦, 你知道嗎
Let's not say anything else.
哦, 其它的什麼也不用說了
I love you.
我也愛你
Not so tight.
哦, 別抱的這麼緊！
-I'm sorry, give me one more chance. -Okay.
-對不起, 再給我一次機會  -好吧
Okay.
好吧
I'm sorry. Just go. Just go. I can't. I can't.
走吧, 走吧 我控制不了自己
-So I guess you're next. You ready? -I don't think so.
-看來你是下一個了 準備好了沒有？ -還沒有
Oh, you're definitely not. I haven't cried like that in years.
顯然你沒有  我幾年都沒有這麼哭過了
You cried yesterday at the 6:00 news.
昨天晚上你還對著六點鐘的新聞哭來著
That old woman was being scammed by her mechanic.
那個老太太被人騙得好慘！
God, I can't believe she saved me for last.
天哪, 沒想到她居然把我排在最後
Why are they taking so long?
他們倆怎麼還沒說完？
I don't know. But, God, Joey seems to be handling it surprisingly well.
我也不知道  不過看起來喬伊好像沒什麼事兒一樣, 真是意外！
-No! -No! Joey!
-不 -不！喬伊
Okay, here we go.
好了, 輪到我了
-Well.. -Yeah.
-啊, 好吧  -嗯
I think I'm gonna take off.
我想我該走了
I have such a big, big day tomorrow, so..
我明天會很忙, 所以..
-Rach. -Yeah?
-瑞秋. -怎麼?
Aren't you forgetting something?
你是不是忘了什麼事?
-Oh, right. Ross. -Yes?
-哦，對了. 羅斯 -怎麼?
I forgot to write your mom a birthday card. Would you please do that for me?
我忘了給你媽媽寫生日賀卡了.你能幫我寫一張嗎?
-Sure. -Thank you.
-當然. -謝謝.
Oh, you guys, this was an amazing night. Thank you so much.
哦, 真是奇妙的夜晚啊, 非常感謝
I love you.
我愛你們
Good night.
晚安
What?!
什麼?!
I don't get a goodbye?
都不和我說再見的?
Lucky bastard.
你這個幸運的混蛋
Unbelievable. She says goodbye to everyone but me!
我簡直不敢相信.... 她跟你們每個人告別, 卻不跟我說
Well, maybe she thought that with all of your history, it could be..
也許她覺得你們這麼多年的默契... 一切都...
-you know, implicit. -Well, it needs to be "plicit."
-「盡在不言中」了呢 -啊! 那起碼需要「言」呢
You know, maybe she was just really spent from our talk.
你知道, 也許她和我們講話花費不少體力
-It was pretty intense. -Yeah, mine too.
-真是非常的熱烈啊 -對啊, 我的也是
-Mine was a humdinger. -Okay!
-我的很了不起 -沒錯
All right, let's think about this. I mean, there's gotta be an explanation.
我們好好想想, 肯定是有什麼原因的
-Did you do anything to make her mad? -No, I don't think so.
-你是不是惹她生氣了？ -沒有啊
You didn't, say, borrow her Girls Gone Wild video and never return it?
那你有沒有借她的"Girls Gone Wild"錄影帶 而且又不還
Really? Now?
真的? 現在?
I mean, don't I deserve anything? I mean, a few tears, a cursory hug?
我是說, 我真的那麼無足輕重嗎？ 哪怕是幾滴眼淚, 一個簡單的擁抱...
Not from you!
不是跟你抱！
Ross, if you're this upset, you should go and talk to her.
羅斯, 如果你這麼在意, 你應該去跟她直說
And say what? You owe me a goodbye?
說什麼啊？說「你還沒跟我告別呢」？
-I mean, he's got more pride than that. -The hell I do!
-他的自尊心往哪兒放？ -什麼自尊心, 見鬼去吧
-I don't get a goodbye? -What?
-連再見都不跟我說？ -什麼？
Everyone gets a goodbye but me? What do I gotta do to get a goodbye?
你跟其他人都告別過了, 為什麼沒有我？ 到底要我做什麼你才捨得跟我說句再見？
Be best friends with you? Go out with you?
和你做好朋友？和你約會？
Have a baby with you?
跟你生個孩子？
Oh, wait a minute. Wait a minute! I did all those things!
哦, 等一下, 等一下, 這些我好像都做過！
-Ross.. -Or maybe I'm just not giving you..
-羅斯   -哦, 也許我應該體諒你一下
enough credit. I mean, it is difficult to say goodbye to five people.
也許連續跟五個人說再見是太困難了一點, 嗯...
Goodbye, goodbye, goodbye, goodbye, g..
再見, 再見, 再見, 再見, 再...
It's physically impossible!
哦, 簡直不可能啊！！！
You know what? After all we've been through..
你知道麼, 我們這麼多年的感情
I can't believe this is how you want to leave things between us.
我真沒想到這就是你想要的結局
Have a good time in Paris.
祝你在巴黎一切順利
Rach, I know this may not be the best time..
瑞秋, 我知道現在可能不是最佳時機.
but Joey's going over the balcony again. Could you just come talk to him?
但是喬伊又去陽台了, 你能過來和他談談嗎?
-I hope Ross isn't too upset. -I'm sure he's not more bummed out..
-我希望羅斯不會太沮喪  -我肯定
-than I am. -Tell me about it.
-我比他難過  -誰說不是呢
Well, you can't say we don't know how to throw a party.
看來我們的聚會辦得不錯！
I think I'm gonna head out.
我要撤了
-Where do you think you're going? -I thought I was going home to bed..
-你打算去哪兒？ -我打算回家睡覺
but I'm sensing there's something less fun for me to do here.
不過現在我感覺到有人要逼我留下來了
We're moving, and we got a lot of packing to do.
我們馬上就要搬家了, 有很多東西需要收拾
-It'd be great if you guys could pitch in. -Joey and I can finish up the guest room.
-如果你們能來幫忙就太好了  -喬伊和我可以繼續收拾客房
Yeah, good idea.
是啊, 是啊, 好主意
Oh, no. You and Phoebe are gonna help me in here.
噢, 不行  你和菲比留在這兒幫我
You couldn't be cool.
你就不會裝得冷靜一點
We're gonna start in the kitchen.
好的, 讓我們從廚房開始
Plates get put into plate protectors and stacked 10 to a box.
首先盤子放在盤套裡, 然後十個一組裝箱
The silverware gets bundled in rubber bands and then bubble wrapped. Got it?
銀器要先用橡膠膜捆上, 然後用塑料泡沫包上  明白了沒有？
-Yeah. -Good. I need you to be careful..
-明白了  -好 , 你們要小心一點
and efficient. And remember, if I'm harsh with you..
同時動作要快 記住, 如果我朝你們叫喚...
it is only because you're doing it wrong.
那肯定是你們哪裡做錯了
Hey, Mon, I think I figured out whose handcuffs they are.
嘿, 莫妮卡, 我想我知道手銬是誰的了..
-You did? How? -Well, I was cleaning out the closet..
-你怎麼知道的？ -我剛才在收拾櫃子的時候..
and I found some pictures of them..
發現了這個
-being used. -Oh, my God, let me see.
-一些相關的照片  -天哪, 讓我看看
Who's that dirty old lady?
那個又老又髒的女人是誰啊？
Monica's grandmother.
莫妮卡的祖母
Oh, my God. Nana liked it rough!
哦, 天 原來她老人家喜歡這調調！
-Hi. -Hey.
-嗨 -嘿
-What are you guys looking at? -Oh, just normal pictures..
-你們在看什麼？ -哦, 只是普通的照片..
of our regular family not having sex.
正常的家庭卻沒有做愛
-Oh, here, have a seat. -Yeah.
-來, 坐下, 坐下  -好 .
-How was your night? -Oh, it was okay.
-今天晚上過得怎麼樣？ -還不錯.
I went to a movie with my cousin then out for dinner.
我和我堂兄去看了場電影 然後一起吃了晚飯
We went to this place that had..
我們去的餐廳...
Anyway, they had these really amazing cheeseburgers.
噢...噢... 總之呢, 那家餐廳的起司漢堡真是棒極了
-Erica, are you okay? -Yeah, you know, maybe I ate too much.
-艾瑞卡, 你是不是不舒服？ -有一點 可能是我吃多了
I keep getting these stomachaches. They come and go every few minutes.
我的胃一直有點疼, 每隔幾分鐘就疼一下
-Oh, my God. -Relax, we'll just get her some antacids.
-哦, 天哪  -別緊張, 我們給她點胃藥就行了
She doesn't have a stomachache! She's in labor!
那不是胃痛, 那是陣痛的症狀！！！
-Oh, my God! -Yeah, you gotta get to the hospital!
-哦, 天哪！ -要趕快送她去醫院！！！
Chandler, get the coats! Erica, let's go! Phoebe and Joey, keep packing!
錢德去拿外套, 艾瑞卡我們馬上出發  菲比和喬伊, 繼續收拾！
Oh, my God, we're gonna have a baby.
哦, 天哪, 我們要有孩子了！
We're gonna have a baby!
Oh, my God, we're gonna have a baby!
哦, 天哪, 我們要有孩子了！
Oh, God, I've gotta sit down! I've gotta sit down!
哦, 我的上帝, 我得坐一下, 我得坐一下
-Honey, it's gonna be okay. -You can do this. Just breathe.
-親愛的, 一切都會很順利的  -你一定能撐過去的, 深呼吸
Okay. Okay.
好好好
Okay, I feel a little better.
我覺得好一點了
Are you sure?
噢...你真的好一點了麼？
-Yes, I'm sure. Oh, honey, let's go. -Okay.
-是的, 我沒事 親愛的, 我們走吧  -好
-Come on, let's go. -Okay, bye, everyone!
-哦, 親愛的, 走吧 -大夥兒再見了！
-We're having a baby! -Good luck!
-我們就要有孩子了 -好運！
-Chandler, wait, wait, wait! -What?
-錢德, 等等, 等等 -幹嗎?
If you get a second, find out where she got that cheeseburger.
如果她有空的話 幫我問問 她的那個起司漢堡是在哪兒買的
"Dear, Judy.
"親愛的.朱迪
Happy birthday, love Rach.."
生日快樂, 愛你的瑞秋.."
No. You know what? I'm not doing this.
不行, 你知道嗎? 我做不來這個
You think I didn't say goodbye to you because I don't care?
你真的以為我不跟你告別是因為我不在乎你？
That's what it seemed like.
看起來就是這樣啊
I cannot believe that after 10 years you do not know one thing about me!
我真不敢相信, 都十年了 你居然對我連最起碼的瞭解都沒有
-Then why didn't you say something? -Because it is too damn hard, Ross!
-那你倒說說, 你為什麼不跟我告別呢？ -因為...那對我來說太困難了, 羅斯
I can't even begin to explain to you how much I am gonna miss you.
一想到我會那麼掛念你 我根本就開不了口
When I think about not seeing you every day, it makes me not want to go.
每當我想到自己不能再天天看到你 我就不想走了
Okay? So if you think that I didn't say goodbye to you..
如果你以為我不跟你告別是因為...
because you don't mean as much to me as everybody else, you're wrong.
你對我來說不如其他人那樣重要 那麼你錯了
It's because you mean more to me.
對我來說你比他們都重要
So there, all right? There's your goodbye!
好了, 現在明白了吧, 這就是你要的告別
-Rach! -What?
-瑞秋 -幹嗎？
-You keep.. You can't.. -What?
-你...你不...你不能... -不能什麼？
-A little more. -Okay.
-再多塞一點  -哦
-A little more. A little more. -All right.
-再多一點, 多一點 -好
Little more.
再～～來一點
-All right. All right, let's do this. -All right, ready?
-行了 來吧  -好勒 你準備好了麼？
Yep. Now give me your best shot.
好了 記住了要用全力
All right. Here goes.
行 來了
Doesn't work.
一點兒用都沒有...